For Merit Magic Bread.
arrange the decorations
Comfortably waffle cookies
A handy little meal
Kuma and Koray Stream
Almost everyone can see
250 yen to do research in the store
I came to Okinawa for the filming of Yanken-chan
Let's see, cleaning Kojima
This is my first time here.
First of all, this is a place to prepare
It's already amazing!
Beer!
Ta-da!
Amazing!
The house
The house is so nice!
I'd love to spend some time there.
I really want to
It's so nice there.
It's nice weather, isn't it?
Yeah, it was.
It's great.
Make it up.
We've got a full day today.
We'll shoot through day four.
We're shooting there tomorrow.
I'll do my best.
Okay, turn it.
He's running away.
I'm so scared.
He doesn't look okay.
You don't look okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Is he gone?
You scared the shit out of me.
It's so creamy and beautiful.
Thank you so much.
Okay, I'll see you later.
It's so pretty.
Oh, my God.
Amazing.
Pretty, pretty, pretty.
Look at that.
He's adorable.
He's so cute.
He's cute.
Cute, cute.
Yoko Coke
She's adorable.
Yes, it's perfect.
Chilamin
Chilamin.
Better than anyone.
I love a good girl.
They have to be done sometime.
Yes, OK.
Cute.
It looks like a cover.
This is what a cover looks like.
It's like, "This is how you eat.
It's like a "za".
What?
Like this?
Oh, like this!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, the costume... the costume, Mori...
It's very difficult.
She is going to stand out more than me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Rules for Mori!
Oh no.
Oh no!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Too funny!
I think I might have a YouTuber's touch.
That's amazing! I've never seen a whip before.
I wonder if it's possible to have something like this attached to you?
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, wow! It stretches!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's so good! I can't compare it to anything.
Delicious. Not too sweet, not too much. Just a hint of sweetness. Delicious!
Very satisfying. I'll eat it later.
Surprisingly dazzling.
Pretty.
Yes, it feels good.
This is a wampala.
What's a wampala?
What's a Wampala?
It's a little cloudy.A little light overcast
Wampala
Beautiful! So cute!
Now, it's really pretty from here, too!
Beautiful from me too!
And from the back, too...so beautiful!
But you're beautiful from me, too.
Why?
You're beautiful everywhere!
You did it!
Thank you.
You're so cute.
You did it!
Yes, OK. I think it's OK.
Yes, it's OK.
Mr. S on YouTube didn't make it down to these waters.
I'm taking this for cute.
Thank you very much.
Look like you're having fun.
Like having fun?
I haven't done anything like this in a few hundred million years.
Well then.
I'll come by.
Thank you very much.
I'm pulling, I'm pulling.
This is the bottom.
This way down.
All of them.
Like this on the cover.
Indeed.
It looks like it has a pull.
It's new.
If it were a cover, we wouldn't need this batten.
No batten.
He said he didn't need the batten.
He said it looks like a pull.
It looks like a pull.
This one, too.
Yes, perfect.
I can turn it around a bit.
To your mother.
Yes, yes, yes, I can turn it off at the switch.
Oh, I see.
Yes, it's a café.
Yes, it's a cafe.
It's cold
It's cold.
It's cold even though it's Okinawa.
It's cold
The wind is cold.
And I have to go in that pool at night.
It's so cold!
I wish you could measure the water temperature.
It's as cold as ice water.
It's really cold.
I think it might be here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's a little flat.
It's falling.
Maybe turn around a little bit.
Angle of the body
Color it.
Very well.
This one.
Not on the change
Pull up.
Please, come in, master.
Go ahead.
He's cute.
What's the beat?
It's broken.
Oh, no.
You're laughing.
Yes, it's cool.
I'm glad I held off on sleepiness.
If you go to bed early...
I'll finish my face when I go to bed.
I'll figure it out.
So I can take my clothes off now?
Yeah, I think so.
It's not so cold when there's no wind.
I don't like this.
That's a flat surface.
The wind is amazing.
Oh, that's cute.
This one and the tower message are cute.
Here's a version that goes inside.
Cute.
So cute.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
What do you think?
Okay, a little upsetting, like this.
No way. The beach!
Let's try something similar over there.
Like this.
Finally.
How's it look?How is it?
Difficult?
It's hard.
This is great.
I wonder if this is a memory of the Heisei Era.
The weather was really overcast just now.
It's evening, it's already half past 6:00...
Within 6:00, 6:30, it's this bright!
Pictures I want you to take later.
The pictures I want you to take
It won't change.
It's so beautiful!
What?
That was so beautiful.
Is this what your face looks like when you turn around?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cute, cute, cute.
Cute style
cute cute cute cute
nice boss
Cute
Eh?
Oh, cute and adorable
It's insanely beautiful.
Yes, OK. It's cute.
Let's take a look.
Super beautiful, the sunset.
It's here, it's here.
That's good.
It's nice.
Even when it was covered by clouds for a moment.
I've been doing gravure for more than 10 years now.
I've been doing gravure by myself for the first time, maybe almost the first time.
For the first time, there's no clothes.
Definitely a one-piece, but today, oh my God!
Swimsuit only!
Please look forward to the next time!
Aaaaah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
My feet hit the ground.
Too much hand gesture.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
Wagyu stuff
by H.
Cute butt!
Isn't it cute?
It's amazing.
Oh, my God.
You have a nice ass.
It's all butt.
All butt.
Buttocks.
Butt. - Butt.
I can't believe we're done filming. Are you okay?
I'm taking a shower, but I'm too scared to start.
Well, that's it for today. Tomorrow morning at 1:00, we're off before 7:00.
I've got one more dress tomorrow. It's almost like one more dress, so I'm gonna do my best.
I'll have dinner after all this time. Thank you for your hard work.
Good morning.
First watermelon of the year!
Great! I'm so happy!
My favorite!
So happy!
These grapes and blueberries are so good too!
I'm going to try again today.
Yes, it is!
The wind is playing tricks on us.
Something here.
Inside.
Right here.
Cute
Cute.
This is YabaCawa.
It's YabaCow.
It's Yabacawa
Thank you for watching!
These flutters. Flutters.
Oh, this one. Flutter, flutter.
It's so beautiful. I think it's so beautiful.
It's Yabasawa. It's Yabasawa.
Cute, cute.
Otsuchi.
I can go on a comment patrol if you put the back side out.
I get a lot of super crappy comments on Gladia's videos.
I'll take another shot of it and do the comment patrol.
You can use it many times in various patterns.
It's also in the rush.
There's definitely glitter in the eyes.
Stay tuned for the next Rush video!
See you soon!See you soon!
Sleepy when the heart stops
My back legs are killing me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, it's cold.
That's what everyone thinks.
I got mad when I got mad.
Oh, there he is.
Did you find him? Did you find him?
There he is.
Nice weather.
Come on, come on, come on.
Don't fall.
I think I'm gonna die. I really think I'm gonna die.
Thank you very much.
It's warm.
Watch out.
I'm gonna lose my balance and fall backwards.
My feet are frozen.
I'm not as strong as I should be.
the end
When you leak the front,
Oh, cute, a little too much cut
Yes, a little too much.
Yes, it's cute.
Akimoto, you're at your limit. It's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's possible, isn't it?
Soon. No, it's likely.
It'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
The back is right here.
It's a cool blue.
Just a little bit.
I'm done!
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
That's cool. That's cool.
Thank you for finishing.
Well, that's it.
Two days of filming has been completed!
It's going to be released on June 1st.
Please check it out at the main market!
I've been doing gravure for over 10 years now.
I've been doing gravure for more than 10 years and I still haven't worn a bathing suit yet.
I was like, "There's a situation I've never done before.
It was fun!
I'm going to have dinner and buy some souvenirs to take back home.
So thank you very much for watching the video!
Please check out Young Jump when it comes out!
I'm looking forward to hearing your comments!
That's all for now, this is Yuki Washiwaki aka Yukirin!
See you soon!